myfantasyleague.com 2000-12-02

# Fantasy Football at myfantasyleague.com: Our Privacy Policy

---  

|   
  
**Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:**
    Our Commitment To Privacy
    The Information We Collect
    How We Use Information
    Our Commitment To Data Security
    Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
    How To Correct Your Information
    How To Contact Us
 **Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the myfantasyleague.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

    Name 
    Address 
    Email address 
    Phone number 
    Credit/Debit Card Information 

On your league page, you may voluntarily enter contact information that makes it easier for league memebers to contact you, including: 

    Name 
    Email address 
    Daytime Phone Number 
    Evening Phone Number 
    Fax Number 

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We do not, in any manner, use the information voluntarily entered on your league page. It is important to realize that anyone (not just your league members) may view the contact information you enter on your league page. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that _X_ number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that _Y_ number of men and _Z_ number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Correct Your Information**

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [support@myfantasyleague.com](mailto:support@myfantasyleague.com)  
  
* * *  
  
advertise with us | features | reports | faqs | support | compare | purchase   
[demo](http://fflnet.myfantasyleague.com/fflnet1999/home/0001) | news | mailing list | contact us | home
